Mengqi Wang

Web Developer ———

÷ +1 801 550 9772

() wmq516@gmail.com

Salt Lake City, UT

OVERVIEW

I am a web developer with experience in PERN stack. My interest in problem solving and creativity led me to web development. I bring a growth mindset and strong communication skills. My experience in education and event coordination also make me work well with other people.

PORTFOLIO

Portfolio

GitHub

LinkedIn

PROJECTS

Everest International Education

GitHub: a full-stack teaching job web app Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node, PostgreSQL, Express

Open Garden

GitHub: a full-stack listing app to share homegrown vegetables Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node, PostgreSQL, Express

For Drizzle

GitHub: a web app that recommends whether you should water plants Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery

Country Capital Quiz

GitHub: a country quiz app that tracks scores Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTMI

CSS

JavaScript

React

NodeJS

PostgreSQL

Express

jQuery

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer Volunteer / Just Utah Coders

03/2020 - Present

- Quickly on board <u>utahexpungements.org</u> with minimal supervision;
- Worked with Salt Lake County Expungement Coordinator to improve the forms tool:
- Identified and fixed inconsistent data keys to improve cross-form data population;

K-12 Community Outreach Coordinator / Confucius Institute, University of Utah 07/2019 - Present

- Plan and manage educational and cultural events of diverse content summer camps, performance, academic talk and teacher training.
- Plan and implement event promotion, often bilingual, utilizing personal and professional connections, social media, community-specific channels;
- Understand and coordinate the complex needs of different events, from a
 dozen attendees to a few hundred, from one-day events to multi-day
 events, one-site to multi-site, including adults and minors, and people of
 different linguistic and cultural backgrounds;
- Delegate event aspects to a team up to 10 people;

EDUCATION

Engineering Nights & Weekends *Thinkful, 2019*

MA in Linguistics University of Utah, 2013-15

MA in Linguistics Chinese University of Hong Kong, 2011-12

BA in English Huazhong Uni of Science & Technology 2007 - 2011